olxtube.com 2014-03-11

# Privacy Policy » Olxtube the way to share your favorite

**DMCA Policy**

olxtube.com respects the others, and in return it also wants the same. olxtube.com doesn’t allow copyright inferinging activities on its website. olxtube.com will remove all the copyright content, and have the rights to terminate the account of the user who will involve in such activities. olxtube.com also have the right to remove/suspend the account of such users who violates our terms and conditions. 

**Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998**

In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, olxtube.com will respond expeditiously to claims of copyright infringement that are reported to olxtube.com. If you believe your content has been copied in any way, please provide the olxtube.com the following information: 

1\. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed; 

2\. Identification of the copyright work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at the Website; 

3\. Information reasonably sufficient to permit olxtube.com to contact the complaining party, including a name, address, telephone number and, if available, an email address at which the complaining party may be contacted. 

4\. Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit olxtube.com to locate the material; this must be in the form of a direct URL to the page on which the infringing content is linked. This detail is necessary as each video can have multiple links and to protect relationships with our partners we wish to avoid deleting authorized links in error. 

5\. A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; and 

6\. A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. 

Send the written infringement notice or contact us 

Please allow 1-2 business days for an email response. Note that emailing your complaint to other parties such as our Internet Service Provider will not expedite your request and may result in a delayed response due the complaint not properly being file 

**Privacy Statement**

This privacy policy sets out how olxtube.com uses and protects any information that you give olxtube.com when you use this website. 

olxtube.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

olxtube.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information: 

1\. Name and job title 

2\. contact information including email address 

3\. demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests 

4\. other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers 

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

1\. Internal record keeping. 

2\. We may use the information to improve our products and services. 

3\. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 

4\. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. 

**Security:**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How we use cookies:**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Links to other websites:**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.   
**  
Controlling your personal information:**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

1\. whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes. 

2\. if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at admin@olxtube.com 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
